[SCANNER BEEPS]
(Sheldon:)Socks, one pair, cotton, argyle, blue.
(Sheldon:)What on earth are you doing?
(Raj:)Whatever it is,
I'm guessing we're doing it wrong.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, this is the Coast Starlight...
(Sheldon:)...one of the great American trains operating
on one of the classic American routes.
(Sheldon:)On this side,
you'll see panoramic ocean vistas...
(Sheldon:)...inaccessible
to any other form of transportation.
(Sheldon:)While on your side
you'll be treated to 350 miles...
...of Costcos, Jiffy Lubes and cinder block
homes with above-ground pools.
- Come on, Raj.
- What's wrong with Jiffy Lubes?
(Sheldon:)No.
- Why not?
- That's over the wheelbase.
(Sheldon:)Are you completely unfamiliar
with the suspension characteristics...
(Sheldon:)...of a pre-1980 Pullman-built
Superliner Deluxe passenger coach?